We use cookies to understand how you use our site and to improve your experience. This includes personalizing content and advertising. To learn more, [click here](https://www.theconversionpros.com/privacy "link"). **By continuing to use our site, you accept our use of cookies.**

I Accept

Menu Button

Close Button

**Privacy Policy**  

---------------------

TCP Takes your privacy very seriously, **as should you.** Below is our Privacy Policy

THE CONVERSION PROS PRIVACY POLICY
==================================

This Privacy Policy went into effective as of November 2015. This policy was last updated October 3, 2023.

The Conversion Pros, Inc. provides a cutting edge online marketing system for business owners and entrepreneurs to establish an online presence for their business, find their audience, build relationships with their clients and market their products to their clients. Our marketing system provides our Clients with email broadcasting, Auto Responders, Text/SMS, capture pages, sales funnels, and many other tools to choose from. As prospects respond back to or input their information into one of the marketing tools our Clients use within our system, data is collected on the prospects. Should the prospect become a direct Client of The Conversion Pros, Inc., more information is collected at the time of sign up.

The Conversion Pros, Inc. plays multiple roles when it comes to our relationship with the data collected:

* When we provide our services to our Direct Clients, we are gathering personal information on them and acting as the Data Controller. In the Data Controller scenario, The Conversion Pros, Inc. makes the changes to the data per the request of our Direct Client.

* When our Client uses our services to contact and gather information from their own clients (Data Subjects), the data collected in our system is controlled by our Client, therefore, we are acting as the Data Processor. In the Data Processor role, our Clients send us requests for the information changes on behalf of the Data Subjects. Therefore, the Data Subjects need to contact our Clients directly for any data changes needed.

* The Conversion Pros, Inc. has an Affiliate program, that compensates our Clients for referring other Clients to use our services. The referred Client becomes a direct Client of The Conversion Pros, Inc. In this scenario, The Conversion Pros, Inc. is acting as the Data Controller and makes changes to the data collected from the referred Client, per the request made directly from the referred Client.

1.  Our Commitment to Privacy.

At The Conversion Pros, Inc., we respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously. This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and service, [www.theconversionpros.com](http://www.theconversionpros.com/) owned and operated by The Conversion Pros, Inc. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our Clients/Members have engaged us.

2.  What Information is Collected

(a) Information You Provide to Us:

We collect the Personally Identifiable Information you choose to enter on various pages of our website, or that you may choose to give us in some other way (such as by email, physical mail, or by telephone). For example, you will be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information when you register or make a purchase.

The types of personal information that we seek to collect from you, for purposes of our website, include your first and last name, e-mail address, physical address, and telephone number, along with any other related relevant information (referred to herein collectively as "Personally Identifiable Information").

You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features.

**“Customer Of The Conversion Pros”  
**All account information for our Clients is held in strict confidence.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your information or allow the data to be used for reasons other than that for which it was provided. We only collect information like your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information so we can provide the marketing services described on our website.

**“Affiliate Of The Conversion Pros”**  
If you chose to be an Affiliate with The Conversion Pros, Inc., we will collect your name, address, phone and fax number, email address, and any other information you provide. For our US Affiliates we also collect tax ID number or SSN, which allows us to meet United States federal tax requirements. This information is held in strict confidence. We collect this information only so we can generate your commission checks. We do not sell your information or allow the data to be used for reasons other than that for which it was provided.

**“Subscriber To An Email Or Text/SMS List Managed Through The Conversion Pros”  
**Your email address, name and any other information you provide, such as address and phone number you provide to our Clients, are held in strict confidence. We only keep your information so that our Client, whose email list you subscribed to, can contact you.

The Conversion Pros, Inc. does not sell your information or allow our third party vendors/processors to use the data for reasons other than that for which it was provided.

We collect information under the direction of our Clients, and have no direct relationship with you, whose personal data we process. We work with our Clients to help them provide notice to their subscribers concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected.

If you are a subscriber of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by our Client, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. If you are one of our Clients and would like to update your account, please submit a Support Ticket through The Conversion Pros Contact Us page in your back office.

We have no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data we process. We acknowledge that you have the right to access your personal information. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, or opt-out of a list, should direct his or her query to our Client (the Data Controller). If our Client requests that we remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

We may transfer personal information to a third party Text/SMS service that assists us in delivering Text/SMS marketing messages for our Clients. We will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in our Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed in order to provide services to our Clients. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  

(b) Automatic Information:

When you visit a website, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit. This site, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to our site.

(c) “Cookies”:

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser to our website. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows us, our partners, affiliates, and other service providers to recognize you and make your next visit easier and our service more useful to you.

We use cookies to store visitor information (such as items that you add to your shopping cart), record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, and customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie. You can also change your settings to refuse to accept cookies. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited. If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

(d) “HTML 5”:

We use Local Storage such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website use HTML 5 and Flash cookies, to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing local storage data.

(e) “Log Files”:

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to analyze trends, administer our website, track visitors' movements around our website, and gather demographic information about our visitors as a whole. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about our website visitors.

3.  How and When the Information is Used.

The information we collect is used for administering our business activities as follows:

(a) to improve the content of our website;

(b) to notify consumers about updates to our website; and

(c) to contact consumers for marketing purposes for our own business purposes;

(d) we use other third parties, such as a credit card processing company, to bill you for services, and a Text/SMS service to assist in delivering Text/SMS marketing campaigns for both our Clients as well as our own corporate messages. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

4.  How We Protect Your Information.

The privacy and protection of your information is important to us. We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. The affiliated websites may have different privacy practices, and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Your access to some services and content is password protected. We advise that you do not disclose your password to anyone. In addition, we recommend you sign out of password-protected services at the end of your session. You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and the control of this policy, and you agree to waive any claim against us for liability arising from the foregoing activities.

Information about our users is important to us. Access to your information may be provided to third parties who help us perform the services on our website and third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our website. In addition, we may sell our business or buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be transferred along with other assets. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings or similar legal process, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

5.  Methods We Use to Protect Your Information.

We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons.

6.  Children.

This website does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe we have received any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please send in a Support Ticket through your [www.theconversionpros.com](http://www.theconversionpros.com/) Back Office, under the "Resources" tab, then click on "Contact Us".

7.  How You Can Access Your Information.

**“Client Or Affiliate Of The Conversion Pros”**

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personally Identifiable Information. You can request access to all your Personally Identifiable Information maintained by us by logging into your [www.theconversionpros.com](http://www.theconversionpros.com/) Back Office and choosing “My Profile”.

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may request to correct, update, delete, deactivate it, or opt-out of a list by sending in a Support Ticket through your [www.theconversionpros.com](http://www.theconversionpros.com/) Back Office, under the "Resources" tab, then click on "Contact Us". You can also opt-out of a list by clicking the opt-out link that we include at the bottom of all of our emails to our Members/Affiliates, or you can send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://adrian.theconversionpros.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**“Subscriber To An Email Or Text/SMS List Managed Through The Conversion Pros”**  
We are simply the Data Processor in this scenario. We have no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data we process. We acknowledge that you have the right to access your personal information. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, or opt-out of a list, should direct his or her query to our Client (the Data Controller). Any requests we receive directly will be forwarded to our Client. If our Client requests that we remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed in order to provide services to our Clients. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  

8.  Consent.

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.  

9\. Testimonials.

We post customer testimonials on our website, which may contain personal information. We do obtain our Clients' consent to post their name along with their testimonial prior to posting the testimonial on our website. However, if you wish to request the removal of your testimonial, please send in a Support Ticket through your [www.theconversionpros.com](http://www.theconversionpros.com/) Back Office, under the "Resources" tab, then click on "Contact Us".

10.  Changes to Privacy Policy.

If we make material updates to our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our information practices, we will post those changes to our website for your review. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practice

11.  EU-US Data Privacy Framework, the UK Extension to the EU-US DPF and Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework.

The Conversion Pros, Inc. complies with the **EU-US Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF)** ,the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the  **Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF)** as set forth by the US Department of Commerce.  
  
The Conversion Pros, Inc. has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-US. DPF  
  
The Conversion Pros has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)  
  
Among other things, the DPF Principles describe our obligations with respect to personal information that we transfer to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If The Conversion Pros, Inc. transfers your personal information to third parties, The Conversion Pros, Inc. will remain responsible and liable to you if the third party processes your personal information in violation of the DPF Principles, unless The Conversion Pros, Inc. proves it was not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. The Conversion Pros, Inc. complies with the DPF Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, the UK, and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Data Privacy Framework, The Conversion Pros, Inc. is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, The Conversion Pros, Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  Note that at this time The Conversion Pros does not share data with non-agent third parties or permit its usage for purposes other than those for which the information was originally provided. If this practice should change in the future, we will update this notice to identify those third parties and provide individuals with opt-in or opt-out choice as appropriate.

Pursuant to the Data Privacy Frameworks, EU, UK and Swiss individuals whose data has been transferred into the US have the right to access that data and to amend, correct or request deletion of information that has been handled in violation of the Principles. For more information on how to exercise that right please refer to section 7 of this policy, “How You Can Access Your Information.”  
  
In compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) Principles, The Conversion Pros, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to the Data Privacy Framework. European Union, United Kingdom, and Swiss individuals with DPF inquiries or complaints should first contact The Conversion Pros, Inc. at:  
  
E-mail: [\[email protected\]](https://adrian.theconversionpros.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
  
or  
  
Mail:  
  
The Conversion Pros, Inc.  
701 S. Carson St, Ste 200  
Carson City, NV 89701  
USA  
  
The Conversion Pros, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Data Privacy Framework program to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, Data Privacy Framework Services, operated by BBB National Programs. If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [https://bbbprograms.org/programs/all-programs/dpf-consumers/ProcessForConsumers](https://bbbprograms.org/programs/all-programs/dpf-consumers/ProcessForConsumers) for more information and to file a complaint. This service is provided free of charge to you.

If your DPF complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/G-Arbitration/Procedures-dpf?tabset-35584=2](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/G-Arbitration/Procedures-dpf?tabset-35584=2)

12.  Effective Date.

This Privacy Policy went into effective as of November 2015. This policy was last updated October 3, 2023.  

13.  Contact Us.

You may contact us concerning this Privacy Policy by sending in a Support Ticket through your [www.theconversionpros.com](http://www.theconversionpros.com/) Back Office, under the "Resources" tab, then click on "Contact Us". 

You may also contact us concerning this Privacy Policy at the following e-mail address: [\[email protected\]](https://adrian.theconversionpros.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

​​​​​

**The Conversion Pros, Inc.**  
701 S Carson St, Ste 200  
Carson City, NV 89701

Phone: [(877) 888-2871](tel:8778882871)

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://adrian.theconversionpros.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Menu Button

Close Button

© COPYRIGHT 2022, TheConversionPros.com
